Processing your request ....Cancel Request

You are here: [Careers](https://careers.slb.com/) > SLB Recruitment Privacy Statement

#### Recruitment Privacy Statement

In using this Recruitment website personal data that you provide to, or that is collected from you by SLB Limited and its group companies (“SLB”) will be stored and processed solely by SLB,  

For the purposes of the Data Protection Directive (the "Act") the data controller is SLB Limited  

Collection of Information  

This Recruitment website privacy statement notifies you that, subject to the Act, SLB may ask you to provide and will process your personal data, and in some cases your sensitive personal data, which may include the following:  

• Personal details (e.g. name, address and contact details).  

• Nationality (optional)  

• Academic and vocational qualifications, skills and competencies.  

• Resume/CV documents that support your job applications.  

• Employment history.  

• Job application history.  

You can update, amend or add to your data at any time by accessing the Recruitment website by using your user name and password.  

Storage of Your Personal Data  

The data that SLB collects from you may be transferred to, and stored at, and processed outside of the European Economic Basin ("EEA"). By using this E-Recruitment website and submitting your personal data you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. You can withdraw your agreement at any time by deactivating your account, which will mean you will be unable to continue using the Recruitment website.  

SLB takes all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Recruitment Privacy Statement . All information you provide to SLB is stored on SLB’s secure servers.  

You are responsible for keeping your user name and password for this Recruitment website confidential and you should not share them with anyone.  

Except where required by law or otherwise agreed with you, the data collected through the Recruitment website about you will be held for a maximum of two years from the date you last used your account.  

Uses and Disclosure of the Information  

SLB uses the information held about you in the following ways:  

• To be considered in support of your job applications.  

• To support any offer of engagement and induction to the SLB  

• As the basis for your employee record.  

• Anonymous data may be used to ensure compliance with equal opportunities and employment legislation.  

• SLB may disclose information to companies we employ in support of our recruitment activities. These companies may/will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but may not share that information with any other third party  

Your data will not be used for marketing purposes. Your data may be disclosed and used within SLB Group Companies and its joint venture entities for the above purposes.  

Other than as above, SLB will not disclose your data to third parties provided that it may do so if required by law.  

Your Rights  

You can at any time access your consent or withdraw your consent to the processing of your data by requesting for your account to be deactivated through the Recruitment site. You can also exercise your rights at any time by contacting the recruiting team at Careers@slb.com  

Access to Personal Information  

Where legally required the Act gives you the right to access information held about you.  

Changes to the Recruitment Privacy Statement  

Any changes to this Recruitment Privacy Statement in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.  

Contact  

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Recruitment Privacy Statement should be addressed to DataPrivacy@slb.com

Help

[OK](javascript:__doPostBack('ctl00$ucHelp$modalHelp$lnkButtonOK','') "OK")

© 2022 SLB Limited.
